Downloaded @ subs4free.club
...Dr. Aaron,
dial extension 200, please.
Dr. Aaron, extension 200.
Dr. Burr, 4-1-2-0.
I could lie here forever.
Yeah.
Hey, get your costume
picked out for tonight?
I'm thinking of going as an...
exhibitionist.
Okay. Yeah, that's scary.
Hey, it's the only day of the year I can
wear something slutty and get away with it.
You know, I wish... I wish I knew
a poem or something right now.
Something romantic and deep.
- It's too bad you're flunking English.
- I am not.
Sorry, sorry. Remind me why
you skipped class yesterday again?
I wasn't feeling well.
Right. You threw up all over
your papier-mache. I remember.
You are such a jerk.
What time is it?
- Oh, shit.
- Where you going?
Shit, shit, shit. I have to go
to the clinic and I'm so late.
They want me to pick up a prescription
or something. It's just a follow-up.
Hit me.
- Don't go.
- Later, stud.
Could... come by your place?
I mean, if you want my mom
to snip off your balls.
That's what I thought. Catch you later.
Hey.
You boys know this is private property?
Who's gonna clean that up? Dr. Henry?
Your ass is grass and I'm the lawnmower.
Now, get outta here!
Take those eggs home to your mom.
- See ya later.
- Later, cop!
- Howdy, Mike.
- Hello, princess.
Guess you're not much
of a Halloween guy?
No, I am not. One of these days I'm liable
to shoot me one of those little brats.
Come on, if it wasn't for Halloween
this town probably would just vanish
right off the map.
You got a point there.
- I'll see you later.
- Take care, kiddo.
Wednesday at 3 o'clock.
Thursday at 10:30 a.m.
Alright. Just be sure
to bring any information...
Hey.
- I like your costume.
- I like yours, too.
- I'm... I'm not wearing a costume.
- No, that should be fine.
Bye-bye.
Okay, Dora, he'll see you now.
Happy Halloween.
- That can't be true.
- I'm afraid it is.
Are you sure?
Well, according to your HCG levels...
you're about four weeks in.
No, I... look, I...
There has to be some sort of mistake.
Hey, it just takes one time.
So now we're gonna have to...
we're gonna have to figure out
what to do next.
I'm 17.
Dora...
You're not the first person to have this
happen to before they're ready.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
We can book a follow-up appointment.
For next week.
Okay? Review our options.
We still have time.
But whatever course we do take...
well, we're obligated
to notify a parent.
No way.
Dora...
I understand that...
you may be feeling a wide range
of emotions right now.
And that's very normal.
You can take precautions but...
nothing is ever 100%.
So now we're gonna have to...
we're gonna have to figure out
what to do next.
I'm gonna assume you know
who the father is.
You sure you don't wanna...
wanna talk...
Always taking Halloween nonsense
too far. Dora, Dora, Dora, wait.
This is not the time
to isolate yourself, okay?
People can be a lot more understanding
than you think. And...
You're smart enough to know
that whatever you talk about with me
is strictly confidential, so...
Call me. If you do wanna talk.
Or I can refer you to a specialist.
Thanks.
Don't hesitate to call.
I'll see you next week.
Dr. Aaron, dial extension 200, please.
Dr. Aaron, extension 200.
Dr. Burr, 4-1-2-0.
Dora.
Can you hear me?
There we go.
- Slimy.
- Nice try, Mom.
Alright, killer.
Let's take out all those guts.
- Oh, yeah.
- Get your hands right in there.
- There.
- No, no, in the bowl, Remi.
And tonight, if you didn't know it
by now we will have a blood moon...
- Dora.
- Jesus.
Hey, listen,
there's still one pumpkin left.
We could use that tongue
of yours to carve it.
- Aren't you sick of pumpkins?
- Just staying in the spirit of things.
You should try it some time.
Listen... I want you coming home
at a reasonable hour tonight, okay?
Yeah. I'm not gonna go to the party.
Great. You can come trick-or-treating
with Remi and me.
Yeah, I think I'm just gonna stay home
and watch a scary movie or something.
Here? Just by yourself?
Yeah. So?
Baby.
Listen to me.
You can't be skipping class anymore
to be messing around with what's-his-face.
Messing around?
Just stop, alright?
All I'm saying is it's your senior year
and I would really like
to see you graduate.
You know, Mom, we can't all
be prom queens like you.
Fine, Dora. That's fine, just...
Do me a favor, get your grades up
and at least try and make it to the prom.
Remi, get your shoes on!
- Dora, we're leaving.
- Okay.
And if you really are going
to stay in tonight
I only want trick-or-treaters visiting.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Come on, you. Let's go.
Candy's in the bowl,
if you want to hand it out.
Okay, first we'll go to Sam's house.
Okay? Because his mom said...
Mom? Mom? Hey.
- What is it?
- I just wanted...
I missed class yesterday
just 'cause I wanted to...
- Come on. We're missing the best candies.
- One second, Remi. Hang on.
Baby, look, just...
Go out, okay?
Have fun with your friends.
One day you'll blink
and you won't be a kid anymore.
You can even wear my tiara if you want.
Okay, see you in a couple of hours.
Love you.
Come on, mister, let's go.
Bye!
Well, Jace...
I have... a bit of news.
I'm 17. That can't be true.
There has to be some sort of mistake.
Well, I really hope you didn't have
any plans because... I'm 17. I'm 17.
A bit of news. There has
to be some sort of mistake
Shit.
I'm knocked up. I'm knocked up
and it's great. No, it's horrible.
I'm pregnant.
Okay, Jace.
Nice costume.
You gonna say
trick-or-treat or something?
It's part of the deal.
Okay, whatever.
Happy Halloween.
Enjoy.
Okay, good luck with puberty. Bye.
For the start of the annual Halloween
parade, a long time village tradition.
With a car leading the way,
families made their way down main street
to the heart of the small town.
Their destination was Chestertown Park
where the pumpkin carving competition
was under way.
The mayor was satisfied by the turnout
and excited about this year's event.
Hey, it's Jace. Leave a message.
Hey, it's me.
Are you on your way? Or should
I meet you at the party or something?
Hurry up.
Alright, let me know.
Bye.
Trick or treat.
There's no more candy!
God.
- What?
- Trick or treat.
You really don't give up, do you?
Read my lips. There's no more candy.
So get lost.
I swear, I will...
Remi's pumpkins.
Did you do that?
Answer me, you little freaks.
Mama.
Get the hell out of here.
Seriously?
- Hello, Dr. Henry.
- Hello. Hi.
- Doctor, it... it's Dora Vogel.
- Dora.
Is... is there any way
you could come over? Something...
- Are you alright?
- Something is really wrong.
Where are you? Are you home?
I'll be right over.
Hey.
Hi, honey, it's me.
I'm just checking up.
Yeah.
- Are you guys coming home soon?
- Remi, that candy is for later.
We'll be home... I don't know when, Dora.
This stupid junk-bucket won't start again.
Okay, well...
There are these kids, like,
doing weird stuff outside.
What... what, you mean,
like, pulling pranks?
Well, yeah, and I just heard
someone scream really loudly.
Baby, it's Halloween.
People... people scream.
I know, but they, like,
smashed all our pumpkins
and are throwing eggs at the window.
Honey, I can barely hear you.
Listen, we'll talk when I get back, okay?
No, Mom, wait, wait, wait. Can you...
can you hear me now? Hello?
Mom? Damn it.
Trick or treat.
You want some goddamn candy?
You like the candy then have it.
9-1-1. What's your emergency?
There's been a murder.
My boyfriend's been killed.
They're still outside.
I need you to come quickly, please.
Ma'am, slow down. Tell me
what's happened. I'm gonna help you.
There are kids, I think they're still outside.
I think they're gonna try and break in.
I need you to calm down.
I need you to breathe.
Tell me what your name is.
My name's Dora Vogel.
Oh, God, they killed him. Jace...
That's good, Dora. Just calm down.
I need you to give me your address.
I live on Orley Road.
2-1-0-9 Orley Road.
Please just send the police.
It's important you stay
on the line with me, alright?
- We're sending someone right now.
- Okay.
- Are you still there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
I think they cut the power.
Can you still hear me, Dora?
- Yeah. I... I can hear you.
- Okay. Just stop for a second.
Listen. Do you see anything?
There's... I don't know
what the hell is going on, I think...
Dora, I... listen, I want you
to do something for me, alright?
I want you to secure
all the doors and windows.
I'm really scared.
Did you hear my instructions, Dora?
Secure all the doors and windows.
Do you think you can do that?
- Yeah, yeah. Okay. I can do that.
- Alright.
- One second.
- Relax, sit tight...
and help is gonna be there shortly.
I need you to hold on for a second,
okay? Don't go anywhere.
- Hello?
- I'm still here, Dora. You're doing great.
I'm locking the back door.
I really need you to hurry up because
I don't know what the fuck is going on.
- There's some sort of storm.
- I can't hear you. You're breaking up.
Did you say there's a storm?
Tell me what you see, Dora.
Oh, God!
Hurry up. Just hurry up, please!
Please, please...
I didn't hear you. Can you repeat that?
No, you... I can't hear you.
You have to... you have to speak up.
Dora, are you sure it's not
just some kids pulling a prank?
No, I... you don't understand.
They killed my boyfriend, okay?
This isn't a fucking joke.
Okay, Dora, I know you're upset
but I need you to stay calm...
Hello?
No, no, no, no. Hello!
Stop!
Mommy, hug me.
I like to do a good job.
I'm sleepy.
Mommy, hug me.
I love you. Mommy, goodnight.
Let's play.
Help me. Help me, please.
- They're everywhere, Dora.
- Dr. Henry?
- Get away!
- Go to the back door. The back door.
They're everywhere.
Dr. Henry?
Shit.
Don't go out there. Don't go out there.
Don't go out there.
Damn it.
Dr. Henry?
Oh, my God. Okay, okay.
Okay.
Those kids, they came out of nowhere.
You have to listen to me.
You have your car, right?
Tell me you have your car.
Parked... parked down the road.
- Okay.
- But they're everywhere!
I'm not going back out there.
Okay, come on. Come on.
Okay.
Shit.
- Who are they?
- I don't know.
- Where did they come from?
Dora.
- I'm losing a lot of blood here.
- Okay, let me see.
Oh, my God. Okay, what can I do?
- Okay, what about this?
- No, no. You can't be serious.
- Okay.
- It'll work, it'll work.
Here, here.
Holy shit. Oh, alright.
You're gonna need something
hard and flat so that it... holds.
Flat. Hard and flat. Okay.
Anything.
- That's good, that's good.
- Okay. Okay.
Oh, my God.
- Can you hold this?
- Okay.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
You were in the girl scouts, right?
They kicked me out. Assholes.
Okay. Okay.
Like this?
Okay, okay. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Okay, okay, okay. It's done.
I'm so sorry. Okay?
The cops are gonna be here. The cops
will be here any minute, I promise.
- How soon? How soon?
- Damn... damn soon.
Where's your mother?
She's gonna be home.
She's gonna be home really soon.
She's gonna be home
really soon. Oh, shit.
What are they doing up there?
Just keep that on there.
You're okay.
We should really keep that covered.
Let me see if I can find something.
- Here.
- I'll be okay.
- It's good enough.
- Okay.
Alright.
- What's wrong?
- It's why I called you, I don't...
What?
- What?
- I'm not sure. I think, I think...
What?
- No, it makes no sense...
- Well, tell me what the hell is going on!
Maybe it's an abnormal fetus or...
or a hemorrhage somewhere.
There's something wrong with it.
I can't believe it.
You're already four months pregnant.
What? What the hell are you talking about?
You told me it was four weeks earlier today.
Listen to it yourself.
Dora.
You have to get it out of me. You have to
get it out of me right now. Get it out of me!
I can't. I can't. We need to focus
on getting out of here.
Oh, God... okay, we go to the clinic
and you're gonna get it out of me, okay?
Clinic...
Let's go.
It goes... it goes all the way
up to the kitchen. Go!
- Go.
- You go.
No time to argue. Come on.
Hurry!
Here, here. My car keys.
- What? What?
- In case I don't make it.
Forget the goddamn keys
and just hurry up.
Grab my hand, grab my hand,
grab my hand! Quick!
Hurry up!
No! Let him go!
Dora.
- Mommy, hug me.
Mommy, hug me.
Dora?
Dora can you hear me?
It's me.
Listen...
this is what happens now.
Lights out.
Baby grow.
Dora sleep.
Can you hear me, Dora?
Then we carry you.
It's not far.
Can you hear us, little piggy?
We wait for baby.
Baby you don't want.
Baby we want.
Then baby ready.
Then we cut you.
Blood for baby.
Cut you.
Bleed you. Blood for baby.
Then you'll be gone.
Dora?
Dora, little piggy?
Dora gone.
Blood for baby.
Dora?
- Dora, can you hear me?
- Please, leave me alone.
It's me.
Please, leave me alone!
Dora.
Help.
Dora! Is that blood? Are you hurt?
No, no, Mike. They killed Jace.
They just showed up. They showed up
out of nowhere in costume
and they're trying to kill me.
And I don't know.
They're all over the place.
Alright.
Listen.
Take this. I'm gonna go in there.
I'm gonna have a look, okay?
No, no, no. Don't go, don't go.
Please don't leave me. Please.
Hello? Dora? Dora!
It's Dr. Henry.
He's alive, we have to go inside.
We have to go inside, okay?
- But I want you to stay close to me.
- Okay.
Okay, we have to go
through the back door.
They left Dr. Henry in the basement.
It's right over there.
- Is that one of 'em?
- Yeah.
Dora! Dora, help!
Help.
I'm... I'm alone. They... they're gone.
Dora? Dora.
Mike!
Mike, they... they broke my legs.
They broke my arms.
I can't move. I can't move.
- Dr. Henry?
- Put... put the gun down.
- Dora, tell him to put the gun down.
- Mike...
What are those?
Runes.
This one means harvest.
This one here is... birth.
This one right here means sacrifice.
Wait!
Can we just go to the car
and get the hell out of here, please?
You must have said something,
done something.
What? I didn't fucking invite them
over here to kill my boyfriend.
You're pregnant, aren't you?
You found out about it
this morning at the clinic.
Nobody else knows.
We don't have much time.
They've come before. On the same night.
The same blood moon.
My wife, Sherry.
She was pregnant.
I got a call on the radio.
A call to our house.
A disturbance.
The door was open.
I called her name.
Sherry?
Nothing.
Everything was... I could hear...
smell... I don't know.
Blood upstairs.
In the hallway there was blood...
and... and Sherry
our... our sweet little piggy.
Such hot red blood
it was blood for baby.
Dora?
What?
- Can you hear me?
- Mike.
Fuckers are playing with us.
Please, let's just go.
Here. There's no safety.
Point it at what you wanna
shoot at and fire.
Stay here.
No, no, no, Mike, Mike. Please don't go!
Mike? Mike!
Got ya.
Alright.
Where are ya?
Mike...
- come back.
- Sherry?
Get away from me!
Oh, my God!
Mike!
Mike?
Dora.
Dora!
Remi?
Remi, what are you doing out there?
Let me in.
- But where's Mom?
- Mommy's not here, Mrs. Dora.
- Back off!
- Give us what we came for.
- No!
- You can't stop what's coming.
Give us the baby, you little bitch
- or we'll rip it out of you!
- You're not touching me!
I am starving. You hungry?
I've been eating all day.
I don't know what is up with me.
These things are delicious.
Just needs a little bit of salt.
The salt makes it so much better.
Want some?
No? More for me then.
Shit!
How do you like them bath salts, bitch?
Dora!
- Mike!
- Dora, where are you?
Mike, I'm over here.
Mike!
I could lie here forever.
There has to be some sort of mistake.
Dora?
Dora, can you hear me?
Blood for baby.
Blood for baby...
- Blood for baby.
- Blood! Blood!
- Blood! Blood...
Dora?
You okay?
- I'll get you outta here.
- I thought you were dead.
I thought you were dead.
Dora?
You okay?
I thought you were dead.
I scared 'em off. We gotta go.
What's the matter?
I can feel it moving inside of me.
Alright. Come on, we gotta move.
Alright, steady now.
I can get us out of here.
We just gotta find a road.
What is that?
It's my house.
Mike?
Mike. No, no, no.
Sherry?
Mike?
Don't be afraid.
Isn't it beautiful?
My beautiful, precious child.
Don't be scared.
It's God's creation.
It's a miracle.
Here. Don't be scared.
It's the miracle of life.
I don't wanna hold it.
Isn't it precious?
Dora.
Mommy!
Blood for baby.
Blood for baby...
Blood! Blood!
Blood! Blood...
Blood!
She's awake.
- Baby, you're...
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey.
- Mom, what happened?
It's okay, baby. Everything's okay
now, okay? You're in the hospital.
You're safe now.
The doctor says you're doing
really great. Okay?
- Okay?
- Mom, they were everywhere.
Baby, right now, you just need to rest.
You just need to rest, okay?
It's okay. It's okay.
Just close your eyes. It's okay.
It's okay.
Mom.
I lost your tiara.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
That's okay. That's okay.
That's okay, baby.
You're still my princess, okay?
Even if you did get knocked up
like some filthy street whore.
Why couldn't you just keep
your fucking legs shut?
Mom?
Dora?
Can you hear me?